// CREATING AN ARRY AND PASSING THE NUMBER, QUESTIONS, OPTIONS AND ANSWERS
 let questions = [
    {
       numb: 1,
       question:'Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?',
       answer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
       options: [
             'Lionel Messi',
             'Cristiano Ronaldo',
             'Robert Lewandoski',
             'Karim Benzema'

       ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:'Who won the Ballon Dor in 2021?',
        answer: 'Luka Modric',
        options: [
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Luka Modric',
              'Robert Lewandoski',
              'Karim Benzema'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 3,
        question:'Who won the Most FIFA Ballon Dor Awards?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Lebron James',
              'Robert Lewandoski',
              'Micheal Platini'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 4,
        question:'Who won the Youngest Player to score in a FIFA World cup tournament?',
        answer: 'Pele',
        options: [
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Kylian Mbappe',
              'Pele',
              'Diego Maradona'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 5,
        question:'Which player has won the most UEFA Champions league?',
        answer: 'Karim Benzema',
        options: [
              'Luka Modric',
              'Karim Benzema',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Toni Kroos'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 6,
        question:'Which player has won the most PlayMaker awards?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
              'Luka Modric',
              'Kevin Debruyne',
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Xavi'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 7,
        question:'Who is the all-time leading goalscorer for the German national team?',
        answer: 'Miroslav Klose',
        options: [
              'Lukas Podoski',
              'Thomas Muller',
              'Gerd Muller',
              'Miroslav Klose'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 8,
        question:'Which player has won the most Premier league Golden Boot awards?',
        answer: 'Alan Shearer',
        options: [
              'Mohamed Salah',
              'Harry Kane',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Alan Shearer'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 9,
        question:'Who is the only player to have won the UEFA Champions League with three different clubs as captain?',
        answer: 'Sergio Ramos',
        options: [
              'Paolo Maldini',
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Sergio Ramos'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 10,
        question:'Who is the oldest player to have scored a hat-trick in a FIFA World Cup match?',
        answer: 'Roger Milla',
        options: [
              'David Villa',
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Roger Milla'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 11,
        question:'Who is the all-time leading goalscorer for the Brazil nationl team?',
        answer: 'Neymar Jr',
        options: [
              'Ronaldo Nazario',
              'Pele',
              'Romario',
              'Neymar Jr'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 12,
        question:'Which player has won the most European Golden Shoes?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
              'Luis Suarez',
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Criatano Ronaldo',
              'George Best'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 13,
        question:'Who is the youngest Player to reach 100 goals in the UEFA Champions League?',
        answer: 'Lionel Messi',
        options: [
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Karim Benzema',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Raul'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 14,
        question:'Who is the only player to win World cup, UEFA, Ballon dor in the same year?',
        answer: 'Zinedine Zidane',
        options: [
              'Ronaldinho',
              'Zinedine Zidane',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Platini'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 15,
        question:'Who is the only player to have scored in a UEFA champions League final for two different clubs?',
        answer: 'Samuel Etoo',
        options: [
              'Toni Kroos',
              'Angel Dimaria ',
              'Gonzalo Higuain',
              'Samuel Etoo'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 16,
        question:'Who has won the most Premier League Titles?',
        answer: 'Ryan Giggs',
        options: [
              'Paul Scholes',
              'Roy Keane',
              'Rio Ferdinand',
              'Ryan Giggs'
 
        ]
     },
     {
        numb: 17,
        question:'Who is the most Paid Player?',
        answer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
        options: [
              'Lionel Messi',
              'Karim Benzema',
              'Cristiano Ronaldo',
              'Kylian Mbappe'
 
        ]
     },
 ]